Guide to the Frank H. T. Rhodes papers,1977-1996.
Rhodes, Frank H. T. papers, 1977-1996.
- Series III. 1979-1980
  - Presidential/Administrative
    - Senior Vice President
      - Budget Discussion Papers, 1979-81 (Box 29, Folder 19)
        Tuition; faculty salaries.
      - Budget Discussion Papers, 1979-80 (Box 29, Folder 20)
        Council on Wage and Price Stability.
      - Office of Personnel Services (OPS) - General, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 21)
        Employee relations; affirmative action.
      - OPS - General, 1979-80 (Box 29, Folder 22)
        Sexual harassment; minimum wage.
      - OPS - General, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 23)
        Affirmative action; performance appraisals; employee relations; social security.
      - OPS - General, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 24)
        Performance appraisals.
      - OPS - Collective Bargaining, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 25-27)
        United Auto Workers.
      - OPS - Collective Bargaining, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 28)
        United Auto Workers; United Food and Commercial Workers International Union.
      - OPS - Collective Bargaining, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 29)
      - OPS - Fringe Benefits, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 30)
        Children's Tuition scholarship; retirement.
      - OPS - Fringe Benefits, 1979-80 (Box 29, Folder 31)
        Children's Tuition Scholarship
      - OPS - Fringe Benefits Office of Personnel Services, 1979-80 (Box 29, Folder 32)
      - OPS - Middle Management, 1979-80 (Box 29, Folder 33)
      - OPS - Personnel Planning and Policy Board, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 34)
      - OPS - Personnel Policies and Procedures, 1979-80 (Box 29, Folder 35)
        Performance appraisals; grievance procedures.
      - Physical Education and Athletics, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 36)
        Giamatti, A. Bartlett; Ivy League; Athletic recruiting.
      - Physical Education and Athletics, 1976-80 (Box 29, Folder 37)
        Association for Intercollegiate Athletics for Women (AIAW).
      - Physical Education and Athletics, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 38)
      - Physical Education and Athletics, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 39)
        Athletic recruiting.
      - Physical Education and Athletics, 1979-80 (Box 29, Folder 40)
        Schoellkopf stadium.
      - Physical Education and Athletics, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 41)
        Dowsing, Gretchen S.; Sexual discrimination.
      - Physical Education and Athletics, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 42-43)
      - Physical Education and Athletics, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 44)
        Holland, Jerome H.; Conable, Charlotte.
      - Physical Education and Athletics, 1977-79 (Box 29, Folder 45)
        Lake, Charles W. Council on Physical Education and Athletics.
      - Physical Education and Athletics, 1979-80 (Box 29, Folder 46)
        National Collegiate Athletic Association; Association for Intercollegiate Athletics for Women (AIAW); Athletic eligibility; Title IX.
      - Salaries, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 47)
      - Controller, 1979-80 (Box 29, Folder 48)
      - University Auditor, 1979-80 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Vice President for Financial Aid Planning Services
      - General, 1977-78 (Box 30, Folder 2)
        Salary recovery; Weiss Committee report.
      - General, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 3)
        Weiss Committee report.
      - Institutional Information, 1978-79 (Box 30, Folder 4-6)
      - Planning Services, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 7)
      - Planning Services, 1977-79 (Box 30, Folder 8)
      - Planning Services, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 9)
      - Planning Services, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 10-11)
      - Responsibility Centers Analysis, 1976-79 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Treasurer and Vice President
      - General (Box 30, Folder 13)
        WHCU.
    - Vice President for Campus Affairs
      - General, 1979-80 (Box 30, Folder 14)
      - Campus Store, 1979-80 (Box 30, Folder 15)
      - Conference Director, 1979-80 (Box 30, Folder 16)
      - Center for Religion, Ethics and Social Policy, 1979-80 (Box 30, Folder 17)
      - Cornell United Religious Work, 1979-80 (Box 30, Folder 18-19)
      - Cornell United Religious Work, 1979-80 (Box 30, Folder 20-22)
        Sage Chapel.
      - Dean of Students, 1979-80 (Box 30, Folder 23)
        Discrimination.
      - Dean of Students, 1979-80 (Box 30, Folder 24)
        Discrimination; Psi Upsilon fraternity.
      - Dean of Students, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 25)
        Faculty advising; student mental health
      - Dean of Students, 1978-79 (Box 30, Folder 26)
      - Dean of Students, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 27)
        Hazing.
      - Dean of Students, 1979-80 (Box 30, Folder 28)
        Drinkwater, David; Darling, Ruth; Hazing.
      - Dean of Students, 1979-80 (Box 30, Folder 29)
      - Dining, 1979-80 (Box 30, Folder 30)
        Lacey, Margaret.
      - Housing, 1979-80 (Box 30, Folder 31-32)
        Housing shortage.
      - Interreligious International Ministry, 1977-80 (Box 30, Folder 33)
        Beggs, Robert W.; Mbata, J. Congress.
      - International Student Office, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 34)
      - Department of Public Safety, 1978-80 (Box 30, Folder 35)
        Williams, L. Pierce.
      - Transportation, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 36)
        Langmuir lab.
      - Transportation, 1979-80 (Box 30, Folder 37)
      - University Health Services, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 38)
        Frank E. Gannett Newspaper Foundation; Gannett clinic.
      - University Health Services, 1978-79 (Box 30, Folder 39)
        Wiehl, Sandra; Suicide, student mental health.
      - University Unions, 1979-80 (Box 30, Folder 40)
    - Vice President for Facilities and Business Operations
      - General, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 41)
        Goldwin Smith Hall; Rockefeller Hall.
      - General, 1979-80 (Box 30, Folder 42)
        Goldwin Smith Hall; Rockefeller Hall; submicron facility; campus bridge safety.
      - Planning and Facilities, 1979-80 (Box 30, Folder 43)
        Hydraulics laboratory; Performing Arts Center; Cascadilla Hall.
      - Critical Maintenance, 1979-80 (Box 30, Folder 44)
      - Department of Environmental Conservation, 1979-80 (Box 30, Folder 45)
        Ecosystems Research Center.
      - Energy Conservation, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 46)
        Electric cars.
      - Energy Conservation, 1979-80 (Box 30, Folder 47)
        Fall Creek Hydrogenating facility.
      - General Services, 1979-80 (Box 30, Folder 48)
        Telecommunications.
      - Insurance, 1979-80 (Box 30, Folder 49)
        Not-For-Profit Corporation Law.
      - Real Estate, 1979-80 (Box 30, Folder 50)
        Cascadilla Hall, Psi Upsilon fraternity.
      - Travel Office, 1979-80 (Box 30, Folder 51)
    - Vice President for Public Affairs
      - General, 1979-80 (Box 30, Folder 52)
        Noyes, Nicholas H.; Noyes, Clara R.; Snee, Katherine Reinhardt.
      - Alumni - General, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 53)
        Lake, Charles W.; Kroch, Carl A.
      - Alumni - General, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 1)
        Knight, Lester B.; Weill, Sanford I.; Guerlac, Henry.
      - Alumni - General, 1979-80 (Box 31, Folder 2)
        Uris, Ruth C.; Lindseth, Jon A. Gay alumni association.
      - Alumni - General, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 3)
        Lindseth, Jon A.
      - Alumni - General, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 4)
        Foulkes, Roland A. World Health Organization.
      - Alumni - General, 1979-80 (Box 31, Folder 5)
        World Health Organization.
      - Alumni News, 1979-80 (Box 31, Folder 6)
      - Alumni Office, 1979-80 (Box 31, Folder 7)
      - Cornell Alumni University, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 8)
      - Alumni Trips, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 9)
        Fikes, Lee; Weiss, Jeffrey; Oklahoma City; Tulsa; Dallas.
      - Alumni Trips, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 10)
        Newman, Floyd R.; Lytle, Roy C.; Oklahoma City; Tulsa; Dallas.
      - Alumni Trips, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 11)
        Uris, Harold D.; Friend, James A.; Friend, Emme; Knight, John S.; Florida; writing program.
      - Alumni Trips, 1979-80 (Box 31, Folder 12)
        Carver, Roy J.; Knight, John S.; Uris, Harold D.
      - Alumni Trips, 1979-80 (Box 31, Folder 13)
        Browning, Laurance L.; Browning, Virginia; Pittsburgh.
      - Alumni Trips, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 14)
        Mellowes, Charles N.; Johnson, Samuel C. Milwaukee.
      - Alumni Trips, 1979-80 (Box 31, Folder 15)
        San Diego, Los Angeles.
      - Alumni Trips, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 16)
        Bowmar, Bryce; Knauss, Stuart F.; Seeley G. Mudd Fund; Henry J. Kaiser Family Foundation. San Diego, Los Angeles.
      - Community Relations, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 17)
        Bordoni, Raymond; Power Authority of the State of New York; OPEC; Ithaca Arts Festival; city relations.
      - Community Relations, 1979-80 (Box 31, Folder 18)
        WHCU; Sambo's Restaurant; Biological Sciences building.
      - Cornell Chronicle, 1979-80 (Box 31, Folder 19)
      - Cornell Fund, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 20)
        Olin, Spencer T.; Linowitz, Sol M.; Noyes, Jansen; Rebmann, G. Ruhland.
      - Cornell Fund, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 21)
        Newbury, George A.; Treman, Charles E.; Holland, Jerome H.
      - Cornell Daily Sun, 1979-80 (Box 31, Folder 22)
        Casarett, Alison P.; Montgomery, Michael J.; Tompkins County Human Rights Commission. Discrimination; Gay rights.
      - Cornell University Council, 1979-80 (Box 31, Folder 23)
      - Cornell University Council, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 24)
        Saperston, Alfred M.; Holland, Jerome H.
      - Development - Biographies, 1978-80 (Box 31, Folder 25)
        Eastwick, Joseph L.; Taylor, Catherine Blaffer; Davidson, Gordon; Telluride House.
      - Development - Major Gifts Campaign, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 26)
        Weiss, Stephen H.; Regan, Norma K.
      - Development - Major Gifts Campaign, 1979-80 (Box 31, Folder 27)
        Kiplinger, Austin H.; Olin, Spencer T.; Johnson, Samuel C.; Purcell, Robert W.
      - Development - Major Gifts Campaign, 1979-80 (Box 31, Folder 28)
        Uris, Harold D.; Johnson, Samuel C.; Knight, John S.; Olin, Spencer T.; Olin, John M.; Clark, Hays; Browning, Laurance L.; Lewis, William L.; Bennett, Charles D.; Purcell, Robert W.
      - Development - Major Gifts Campaign, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 29)
      - Development - Major Gifts Campaign, 1979-80 (Box 31, Folder 30)
        College of Arts and Sciences.
      - Development - Miscellaneous, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 31)
        Farrand, Livingston.
      - Development - Miscellaneous, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 32)
        Guerlac, Henry; Grumman, Leroy R.
      - Development - Miscellaneous, 1979-80 (Box 31, Folder 33)
        Clark, Hays; Durland, Lewis H.; Friend, James A.; Grumman, Leroy R.
      - Development - Miscellaneous, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 34)
        Johnston, Frances.
      - Development - Miscellaneous, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 35)
        Routh, Joseph P.; Hertzberg, Benjamin; Hertzberg, Lillian.
      - Development - Miscellaneous, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 36-37)
        Performing Arts Center.
      - Development- Miscellaneous, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 38)
        Grumman, David L.; Phillips, Ellis L.; Performing Arts Center.
      - Development - Miscellaneous, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 39)
      - Development - Miscellaneous, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 40)
      - Development - Miscellaneous, 1979-80 (Box 31, Folder 41)
        Acheson, Miriam F. Labor relations.
      - Development - Miscellaneous, 1979-80 (Box 31, Folder 42)
        Kyle, William D.; Gould, Milton S.
      - Endowment Fund, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 43)
        Schaenen, Nelson; Kunic, Michael.
      - Development - Gifts, 1979-80 (Box 31, Folder 44-46)
      - Development - Gifts, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 47)
        Fuertes, Louis Agassiz; Department of Manuscripts and University Archives.
      - Development - Gifts, 1979-80 (Box 31, Folder 48)
        Gould, Milton S.
      - Public Information, 1979-80 (Box 31, Folder 49)
        Maas, James B.; Johnson, Samuel C. Preparation for Life; admissions.
      - Regional Offices, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 50)
      - Tower Club, 1979-80 (Box 31, Folder 51)
      - University Publications, 1979-80 (Box 32, Folder 1)
      - University Relations Director, 1979-80 (Box 32, Folder 2)
        Cuban immigration; Race relations; African mountain gorillas.
      - University Relations Director, 1979-80 (Box 32, Folder 3)
        Public policy.
      - University Relations Director, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 4)
        Gay rights; Equal opportunity policy.
    - Cornell University Medical College
      - Correspondence, 1978-79 (Box 32, Folder 5)
        Cooper, Theodore; Meikle, Thomas H.; Imperial Medical Center of Iran.
      - Correspondence, 1977-78 (Box 32, Folder 6)
        Imperial Medical Center of Iran.
      - Correspondence, 1977-78 (Box 32, Folder 7)
        Meikle, Thomas H.; Purcell, Robert W.; Luckey, E. Hugh; Corson, Dale R.
      - Correspondence, 1977 (Box 32, Folder 8)
        Luckey, E. Hugh; Iranian relations.
      - Correspondence, 1976-77 (Box 32, Folder 9)
        Swan, Roy C.; Rogosin Kidney Center.
      - Correspondence, 1977 (Box 32, Folder 10)
        Cooper, Theodore; Meikle, Thomas H.; Affirmative action.
      - Dean's Report: 1977, 1978, 1977-78 (Box 32, Folder 11)
      - Dean's Report: 1976, 1976-77 (Box 32, Folder 12)
      - Executive Faculty Council, 1978-79 (Box 32, Folder 13-15)
      - General Faculty Council, 1978-79 (Box 32, Folder 16-18)
      - General, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 19)
        Meikle, Thomas H.
      - General, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 20)
        Retrenchment.
      - General, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 21)
        Rockefeller, Laurance S.; Osborne, Stanley de J.; Cooper, Theodore.
      - General, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 22)
        Osborne, Stanley de J.; Capitation; tuition.
      - General, 1978-79 (Box 32, Folder 23)
        Cooper, Theodore; Osborne, Stanley de J.
      - General, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 24)
        Tuition; capitation.
      - General, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 25)
        Osborne, Stanley de J.; Cooper, Theodore; Tuition.
      - General, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 26)
        Osborne, Stanley de J.
      - General, 1975-78 (Box 32, Folder 27)
        Cooper, Theodore; Niarchos, Stavros S.; Osborne, Stanley de J.; Meikle, Thomas H.; Lambertson, Eleanor C.; Buchanan, J. Robert.
      - General, 1974-79 (Box 32, Folder 28)
        Osborne, Stanley de J.; Cornell University Medical College/Rockefeller University cooperative library.
      - General, 1971-78 (Box 32, Folder 29)
        Winifred Masterson Burke Relief Foundation; Samuel J. and Evelyn L. Wood Foundation; Burke Rehabilitation Center.
      - General, 1977-78 (Box 32, Folder 30)
        Cooper, Theodore; Swan, Roy C.
      - Code of Professional Conduct, 1974-75 (Box 32, Folder 31-32)
      - Miscellaneous Papers, 1973-76 (Box 32, Folder 33)
        Bylaws; rules and regulations.
      - Miscellaneous Papers, 1914-73 (Box 32, Folder 34-35)
        Rules and regulations.
      - Miscellaneous Papers, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 36)
        Marcus, Cyril C.; Marcus, Stewart L.
      - Miscellaneous Papers, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 37)
        Long range planning.
      - Miscellaneous Papers, 1972-73 (Box 32, Folder 38)
        Enrollment trends; grievance procedures.
      - Finances, 1974 (Box 32, Folder 39-40)
        An assessment of the Financial Condition of the Cornell University medical College and its Implications for the Academic Program.
      - Finances, 1974-76 (Box 32, Folder 41)
        Third Century Program.
      - Finances, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 42)
        Report of the Ad Hoc Committee on Capital Financing and Financial Planning.
      - Finances, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 43)
        Financial History of the New York Hospital - Cornell Medical Center.
      - Finances, 1927-53 (Box 33, Folder 1)
      - Budget, 1979-80 (Box 33, Folder 2)
      - Budget, 1978-79 (Box 33, Folder 3)
        Cooper, Theodore; Association of American Medical Colleges.
      - Budget, 1979-80 (Box 33, Folder 4)
        Cooper, Theodore; Investment strategies.
      - Quarterly Review, 1977-78 (Box 33, Folder 5)
        Cooper, Theodore; Meikle, Thomas H.
      - Quarterly Review, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 6)
        SUNY relations.
      - Quarterly Reviews, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 7)
        The Third Century Program: A Statement of the Case for The New York Hospital - Cornell Medical Center.
      - General, 1979 (Box 33, Folder 8)
      - General, 1978-79 (Box 33, Folder 9)
        Department of Genetics; investment strategies.
      - General, 1978-79 (Box 33, Folder 10)
        Meikle, Thomas H.; Osborne, Stanley de J.; Corson, Dale R.
      - General, 1978-79 (Box 33, Folder 11)
        Cooper, Theodore; Osborne, Stanley de J.; Computing services.
      - General, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 12)
        Cooper, Theodore; Sutton Terrace apartments.
      - General, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 13)
        Kersting, Donald L.; Real estate; Third Century Program.
      - General, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 14)
      - General, 1978-79 (Box 33, Folder 15)
        Corson, Dale R.; Osborne, Stanley de J.; Sinclair, David A.; Cooper, Theodore.
      - Board Leadership Meetings, 1979 (Box 33, Folder 16)
      - Board Leadership Meetings, 1978-79 (Box 33, Folder 17)
      - Board Leadership Meetings, 1978-79 (Box 33, Folder 18)
        Osborne, Stanley de J.; Stamp, Neal R.
      - Board Leadership Meetings, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 19-21)
      - Joint Board - Agendas and Minutes, 1977-79 (Box 33, Folder 22-25)
      - Joint Board - General, 1977-79 (Box 33, Folder 26)
        Osborne, Stanley de J.; Corson, Dale R.; Cooper, Theodore; Mandatory retirement.
      - Board of Directors - Agendas, 1978-79 (Box 33, Folder 27)
      - Fundraising, 1977-78 (Box 33, Folder 28)
        Chapman, Carleton B.; Commonwealth Fund; Third Century Program.
      - Fundraising, 1977-78 (Box 33, Folder 29)
        Chapman, Carleton B.; Commonwealth Fund; Third Century Program; Report on Proposed Annual Support Plans for New York Hospital - Cornell Medical Center.
      - General, 1977-78 (Box 33, Folder 30)
        Osborne, Stanley de J.; Luckey, E. Hugh.
      - General, 1977-78 (Box 33, Folder 31)
      - General, 1976-78 (Box 33, Folder 32)
        Osborne, Stanley de J.; Board of Governors; Conflicts of interest.
      - General, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 33)
        Osborne, Stanley de J.; Development annual report, Public Affairs annual report.
      - General, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 34)
        Osborne, Stanley de J.; Cooper, Theodore; Long range financial plan; Nursing School; Board of Visitors.
      - NYH - CUMC Joint Agreement, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 35-36)
      - Commonwealth Fund, 1978-79 (Box 33, Folder 37)
        Chapman, Carleton B.; Library complex.
      - Commonwealth Fund, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 38)
        Chapman, Carleton B.; Division of Cell Biology.
      - Commonwealth Fund, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 39)
        Chapman, Carleton B.
      - Fund Raising and Public Affairs Committee, 1978-79 (Box 33, Folder 40)
        Rockefeller Brothers Fund.
      - Fund Raising and Public Affairs Committee, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 41)
        Third Century Program; Wilson report; Kersting report.
      - Society of the New York Hospital, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 1)
        Corson, Dale R.
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Institute, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence, 1978-79 (Box 34, Folder 3)
        Computing services.
      - Executive Faculty Council - Agendas and Minutes, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 4-5)
      - Executive Faculty Council - Agendas and Minutes, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 6)
        Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center.
      - General Faculty Council - Agendas and Minutes, 1979-80 (Box 34, Folder 7-9)
      - Dean's Report, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 10)
      - General, 1979-80 (Box 34, Folder 11)
        Board of Overseers; Sutton Terrace apartments.
      - General, 1979-80 (Box 34, Folder 12-16)
      - General, 1979-80 (Box 34, Folder 17)
        Niarchos, Stavros S.; Uris, Harold D.
      - Budget, 1979-80 (Box 34, Folder 18)
        Guica, Phillip V.; Cooper, Theodore.
      - Four Year Plan, 1978-80 (Box 34, Folder 19)
      - NYH-CUMC Joint Retreat, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 20)
      - General, 1977-80 (Box 34, Folder 21)
        Niarchos, Stavros S.
      - General, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 22)
        Riker, Walter F.; Osborne, Stanley de J.
      - NYH-CUMC Reorganization, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 23-25)
      - Joint Board - Agendas and Minutes, 1979-80 (Box 34, Folder 26-29)
      - Joint Board - General, 1979-80 (Box 34, Folder 30)
      - Joint Board - General, 1977-80 (Box 34, Folder 31)
        Joint agreement; operating rules.
      - Joint Board - General, 1979-80 (Box 34, Folder 32-33)
        Board of Overseers.
      - Joint Board - General, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 34)
      - Joint Board - General, 1979-80 (Box 34, Folder 35)
      - Joint Board - General, 1975-76 (Box 34, Folder 36)
        Board of Overseers of Harvard College: Committee Assignments; Board of Overseers of Harvard College: Functions and Procedures of the Visiting Committees.
      - General, 1978-80 (Box 34, Folder 37)
        Hertzberg, Benjamin; Hertzberg, Lillian; New, Maria I.
      - Board of Overseers, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 38)
      - Board of Overseers, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 39)
        Burke Rehabilitation Center.
      - Board of Overseers, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 40)
      - Board of Overseers, 1979-80 (Box 34, Folder 41)
        Elliott, John.
      - Board of Overseers, 1979-80 (Box 34, Folder 42)
        Cornell University Announcements: Graduate School of Medical Sciences.
      - Board of Overseers, 1979-80 (Box 34, Folder 43)
        Cornell University Announcements: Medical College.
      - Board of Overseers, 1979-80 (Box 34, Folder 44)
        Medical College financial Report: 1979.
      - Board of Overseers, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 45)
      - Board of Overseers, 1979-80 (Box 35, Folder 1)
        Rockefeller, Laurance S.
      - Board of Directors Agenda, 1980 (Box 35, Folder 2)
      - NYH-CUMC Fund, 1979-80 (Box 35, Folder 3)
      - Commonwealth Fund, 1979-80 (Box 35, Folder 4)
      - Fundraising and Public Affairs Committee, 1980 (Box 35, Folder 5)
        Noyes, Jansen.
      - Society of the New York Hospital, 1978-79 (Box 35, Folder 6)
        Annual Reports: 1978, 1979.
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center - Board of Overseers, 1980 (Box 35, Folder 7)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1979-80 (Box 35, Folder 8-11)
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1979-80 (Box 35, Folder 12-14)
        1979 Annual Report: Department of Medicine.
    - Board of Trustees
      - University Bylaws, 1979-80 (Box 35, Folder 15-18)
      - General, 1980 (Box 35, Folder 19)
        Levin, William A.; Keeton, William T.; Linowitz, Sol M.; Holland, Jerome H.; Campus Council.
      - General, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 20)
        Schaenen, Nelson; McCarthyism (era).
      - General, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 21)
      - Trustee Addresses, 1979-80 (Box 35, Folder 22)
      - Trustee Correspondence, 1980 (Box 35, Folder 23)
        King, Joseph P.; Hatfield, Robert S.; Weiss, Stephen H.; Noyes, Jansen.
      - Trustee Correspondence, 1980 (Box 35, Folder 24)
        Fratt, C. K. Poe; Kiplinger, Austin H.; Stewart, Patricia Carry.
      - Trustee Correspondence, 1979-80 (Box 35, Folder 25)
        Noyes, Jansen; Purcell, Robert W.; Kiplinger, Austin H.; Stevens, Stoddard M.; Livingston, Jacqueline.
      - Trustee Correspondence, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 26)
        Stewart, Patricia Carry; Kiplinger, Austin H.; Conable, Charlotte; Holland, Jerome H.
      - Trustee Orientation, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 27)
      - Trustee Committees, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 28)
        Stamp, Neal R.
      - Academic Affairs Committee, 1979-80 (Box 35, Folder 29-31)
        Palmer, Larry I.
      - Academic Affairs Committee, 1975-79 (Box 35, Folder 32)
      - Audit Committee, 1978-80 (Box 35, Folder 33)
      - Board Nominating Committee, 1979-80 (Box 35, Folder 34)
        Cook, Constance E.; Dullea, Henrik; Noyes, Jansen; King, Joseph P.